baliwww.com 2009-12-31

# Bali Hotel, Bali Villa Accommodation Travel Portal in Indonesia

Access Bali Online, which is sister company of ABL Tours & Travel Ltd., committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Even when you visit us as a visitor and or general user, we stay give our high commitment to make you feel safe and free. In order to contact us, for instance, we provide you with various safe ways which you can prefer and use according to your own conditions. All are in safe and fair way. Please read the following  
policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.   

The two above certificates apply to all sites under Access Bali Online ([http://baliwww.com](http://baliwww.com/)). They state that Access Bali Online has a safe, educational, legal, non-pornographic, non-provocative site. More and accurate information about the two certificates could be found in their own sites at [http://www.icra.org](http://www.icra.org/) and [http://www.thepubliceye.com](http://www.thepubliceye.com/). Please read the following information on how we treat any personal information of our clients.

**Using SSL Method (Secure Socket Layer)**  
All your sensitive and critical information about your personal, financial and other related  
information will be proceed and transmitted in a secure way by our servers. It means that all data will be encrypted before being transferred, and decrypted after being received in order to be able to be understood by human.   

**No Shared Information**  
Actually Access Bali Online and ABL Tours and Travel Ltd. will NEVER share your personal and financial information to others for any reason without written permission from you directly. And Access Bali Online and ABL Tours and Travel Ltd. will NEVER use any information about you to sell and or offer any unintended products and services to you. Your data will be stored safely and ABL Tours and Travel are fully responsible for the safety of the data.

**Keep Your Own Privacy**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are short pieces of data used by web servers to help identify web users. No damage to files or systems. Cookies are only used to identify a web user though they may be used to track a user's browsing   
habits. Note that blocking all cookies prevents some online services from working. Also, preventing your browser from accepting cookies does not make you an anonymous user, it just makes it more difficult to track your usage. 

**Included And Covered With This Privacy Policy**  
The following sites are included and covered with and into this Privacy Policy :  
[http://baliwww.com](http://baliwww.com/) or [http://www.baliwww.com](http://www.baliwww.com/) and or pages under its.  
[http://baliwww.net](http://baliwww.net/) or [http://www.baliwww.net](http://www.baliwww.net/) and or pages under its.  
[http://hotelwww.net](http://hotelwww.net/) or [http://www.hotelwww.net](http://www.hotelwww.net/) and or pages under its.  
[http://bali-plus.com](http://bali-plus.com/) or [http://www.bali-plus.com](http://www.bali-plus.com/) and or pages under its.  
[http://villas-bali.com](http://villas-bali.com/) or [http://www.villas-bali.com](http://www.villas-bali.com/) and or pages under its.  
[http://balibackpacker.com](http://balibackpacker.com/) or [http://balibackpacker.com](http://balibackpacker.com/) and or pages under its.  
[http://asiapacifichotel.com](http://asiapacifichotel.com/) or [http://www.asiapacifichotel.com](http://asiapacifichotel.com/) and or pages under its.  
[http://aseanwww.com](http://aseanwww.com/) or [http://aseanwww.com](http://aseanwww.com/) and or pages under its.   
[http://asianwww.com](http://asianwww.com/) or [http://asianwww.com](http://asianwww.com/) and or pages under its. 

**More About Privacy**  
More information about this Privacy Policy could be asked directly to our [President Director](http://baliwww.com/index/about/contact.html) ([Yahoo! Messenger](ymsgr:sendIM?tanas_aramuk "Click to launch Yahoo! 
Messenger")) or via voice at (62-361) 731520 or 081-2391-2002.
